{
  "openingRemarks": "each operand at most 5",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(5 + 2\\)",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + 0\\)",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 + 5\\)",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 + 1\\)",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 + 5\\)",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 + 3\\)",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + 2\\)",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + 3\\)",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 + 3\\)",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 + 1\\)",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + 1\\)",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + 5\\)",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + 1\\)",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 + 4\\)",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + 4\\)",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + 0\\)",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 + 2\\)",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 + 0\\)",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 + 4\\)",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 + 2\\)",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + 2\\)",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + 0\\)",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 + 1\\)",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 + 3\\)",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + 3\\)",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + 1\\)",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 + 0\\)",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + 3\\)",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 + 0\\)",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + 4\\)",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + 4\\)",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + 5\\)",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + 2\\)",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 + 4\\)",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 + 5\\)",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + 5\\)",
      "answer": "6"
    }
  ]
}
